<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Cameron Briar</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Cameron Briar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:56:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>hello</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 15:56:12 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/hello/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;an-exciting-opportunity-with-los-alamos-national-laboratory&#34;&gt;An Exciting Opportunity with Los Alamos National Laboratory&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a ship in the middle of the sea, I met a couple who work for Los Alamos National Laboratory (LANL). One was a software engineer shipping code to satellites orbiting our earth, and the other was a nuclear engineer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without much of a physics background or knowledge of atomic energy, it was the software engineer&amp;rsquo;s role that interested me most. It sounds incredible (and incredibly frightening) to have an opportunity to deploy code that&amp;rsquo;s embedded into a floating system in space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few days after the ship docked back home, I received a follow-up email from the software engineer pointing to the job postings on LANL&amp;rsquo;s website. The work they&amp;rsquo;re doing is exactly the work that intrigues me. Not only is it incredibly fascinating, innovative, and on the frontier of what humans are capable of &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s good work that&amp;rsquo;s making this place (our planet) better. 100% coinciding with the goals I&amp;rsquo;ve set forth on myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;contingency-plans&#34;&gt;Contingency Plans&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The work I&amp;rsquo;m currently doing is highly relevant and it&amp;rsquo;s critical that it gets documented from conception to production. If there&amp;rsquo;s any chance I&amp;rsquo;ll be able work along side these brilliant minds, I&amp;rsquo;ve got to ellicit my own and demonstrate that my B.S. (not bullshit) is in par with their PhD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;test-area&#34;&gt;Test Area&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34;&gt;def myFun(x):
  return x

y = &#39;echo&#39;
myFun(y)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this is an image of something:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.w3schools.com/css/trolltunga.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Free your mind&#34; title=&#34;Free your mind&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And some list of items:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;three&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>